A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Third Administration, Subseries 37.3 FA439B
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Third Administration, 1967-1970; 3; 115 microform reels 115 microfilm reels.
  - Government
    - International (Reel 48, Reel 49, Reel 50, Reel 51)
      - Nepal (Reel 50)
      - Pakistan (Reel 50)
      - Russia (Reel 50)
      - Sierre Leone (Reel 50)
      - Spain (Reel 50)
      - South Africa (Reel 50)
      - Turkey (Reel 50)
      - Thailand (Reel 50)
      - United Nations (Reel 50)
      - Venezuela (Reel 50)
      - Vietnam Moratorium (Reel 50)
      - Vietnam (Reel 50)
      - Yugolslavia (Reel 51)
      - A-Z (Reel 51)
      - General (Reel 51)
      - Official Visits (Reel 51)
    - City (Reel 51, Reel 52, Reel 53)
      - Albany (Reel 51)
        - South Mall (Reel 51)
        - General (Reel 51)
      - Clinton (Reel 51)
      - Cortland (Reel 51)
      - Cohores (Reel 51)
      - Elmira (Reel 51)
      - Jamestown (Reel 51)
      - Kingston (Reel 51)
      - Lockport (Reel 51)
      - Mount Vernon (Reel 51)
      - Newburgh (Reel 51)
      - New Rochelle (Reel 51)
      - New York City
        - Mayor Lindsay (Reel 51)
        - Ethical Culture School (Reel 51)
        - Police Department (Reel 52)
        - General (Reel 52)
      - Niagara (Reel 52)
      - Poughkeepsie (Reel 52)
      - Rochester
        - 1968-1970 (Reel 52)
        - 1967 (Reel 53)
      - Saratoga (Reel 53)
      - Syracuse (Reel 53)
      - Tonowanda (Reel 53)
      - Troy (Reel 53)
      - Utica (Reel 53)
      - Watertown (Reel 53)
      - White Plains (Reel 53)
      - Yonkers (Reel 53)
      - A-Z (Reel 53)
      - General (Reel 53)
    - County (Reel 53, Reel 54, Reel 55, Reel 56)
      - Albany (Reel 53)
      - Allegany (Reel 53)
      - Bronx (Reel 53)
      - Broome (Reel 53)
      - Binghamton (Reel 53)
      - Buffalo (Reel 53)
      - Cattaraugus (Reel 53)
      - Cayuga (Reel 53)
      - Chautauqua (Reel 53)
      - Chemung (Reel 53)
      - Chenango (Reel 53)
      - Delaware (Reel 53)
      - Dutchess (Reel 53)
      - Erie (Reel 54)
      - Essex (Reel 54)
      - Franklin (Reel 54)
      - Fulton (Reel 54)
      - Genesee (Reel 54)
      - Greene (Reel 54)
      - Hamilton (Reel 54)
      - Herkimer (Reel 54)
      - Jefferson (Reel 54)
      - Kings (Reel 54)
      - Lewis (Reel 54)
      - Livingston (Reel 54)
      - Madison (Reel 54)
      - Monroe (Reel 54)
      - Nassau (Reel 54)
      - New York (Reel 54)
      - Niagara (Reel 54)
      - Oneida (Reel 54)
      - Onondaga (Reel 54)
      - Ontario (Reel 55)
      - Orange (Reel 55)
      - Oswego (Reel 55)
      - Putnam (Reel 55)
      - Rensselaer (Reel 55)
      - Richmond (Reel 55)
      - Rockland (Reel 55)
      - Saratoga (Reel 55)
      - Shoharie (Reel 55)
      - Schuyler (Reel 55)
      - Seneca (Reel 55)
      - Steuben (Reel 55)
      - Sullivan (Reel 55)
      - Tompkins (Reel 55)
      - Ulster (Reel 55)
      - Warren (Reel 55)
      - Washington (Reel 55)
      - Wayne (Reel 55)
      - Suffolk (Reel 55)
      - Westchester (Reel 55)
      - Yates (Reel 55)
      - A-Z (Reel 56)
    - Local (Reel 56)
      - Office of Fire Safety and Training (Reel 56)
      - Police (Reel 56)
      - Municipal Police Training Commission (Reel 56)
      - General (Reel 56)
    - Town (Reel 56, Reel 57)
      - Amherst (Reel 56)
      - Babylon (Reel 56)
      - Bethel (Reel 56)
      - Greenburgh (Reel 56)
      - Huntington (Reel 56)
      - Islip (Reel 56)
      - Orangetown (Reel 56)
      - Ossining (Reel 56)
      - Oyster Bay (Reel 56)
      - Philipstown (Reel 56)
      - Seneca Falls (Reel 56)
      - Tonawanda (Reel 56)
      - A-Q (Reel 56)
      - R-Z (Reel 57)
    - State (Reel 57)
      - California (Reel 57)
      - Colorado (Reel 57)
      - Connecticut (Reel 57)
      - Delaware (Reel 57)
      - Florida (Reel 57)
      - Georgia (Reel 57)
      - Illinois (Reel 57)
      - Indiana (Reel 57)
      - Maryland (Reel 57)
      - Massachussets (Reel 57)
      - Michigan (Reel 57)
      - Minnesota (Reel 57)
      - Nebraska (Reel 57)
      - New Jersey (Reel 57)
      - New York State (Reel 57)
        - Bird (Reel 57)
        - Song (Reel 57)
        - General (Reel 57)
      - North Carolina (Reel 57)
      - Ohio (Reel 57)
      - Oklahoma (Reel 57)
      - Pennsylvania (Reel 57)
      - Rhode Island (Reel 57)
      - Utah (Reel 57)
      - Virginia (Reel 57)
      - West Virginia (Reel 57)
      - Wisconsin (Reel 57)
      - Wyoming (Reel 57)
      - A-Z (Reel 57)
      - General (Reel 57)
    - General (Reel 57)
      - New Citizenship (Reel 57)
      - General (Reel 57)
  - Health (Reel 57, Reel 58, Reel 59, Reel 60, Reel 61)
    - Department of (Reel 57, Reel 58)
      - Commendation, letters of (Reel 57)
      - Interstate Sanitation Commission (Reel 57)
      - General
        - 1970 February-December (Reel 57)
        - 1970 February (Reel 58)
    - Hospitals (Reel 58, Reel 59, Reel 60, Reel 61)
      - Brooklyn Hebrew Home & Hospital for the Aged (Reel 58)
      - Children's Asthma Research Institute & Hospital (Reel 58)
      - Children's Hospital in Buffalo (Reel 58)
      - Harlem Hospital Center (Reel 58)
      - Howard Park General Hospital (Reel 58)
      - Kings County (Reel 58)
      - Mount Sinai (Reel 58)
      - New York Foundling Hospital (Reel 58)
      - New York University Medical Center (Reel 58)
      - Pearl River Hospital (Reel 58)
      - Ray Brook Hospital (Reel 58)
      - Roswell Park (Reel 58)
      - Saint Agnes (Reel 58)
      - Saint Barnabas (Reel 58)
      - United Helpers Home (Reel 58)
      - Veterans Hospital Center (Reel 58)
      - West Haverstraw (NYS Rehabilitation Center) (Reel 58)
      - A-O (Reel 58)
      - P-Z (Reel 59)
      - General (Reel 59)
        - New York City Blue Ribbon Panel (Reel 59)
        - Voluntary Hospitals, Financial Crisis of (Reel 59)
      - Topics (Reel 59, Reel 60, Reel 61)
        - Air Pollution (Reel 59, Frame 103)
        - Alcoholism (Reel 59, Frame 219)
        - Birth Control (Reel 60, Frame 11)
        - Measles (Reel 60, Frame 28)
        - Pesticides (Reel 60, Frame 35)
        - Pollution (Reel 60, Frame 61)
        - Rat Control (Reel 60, Frame 73)
        - Solid Waste Refuse Disposal (Reel 60, Frame 96)
        - Water Pollution Sewage (Reel 60, Frame 117)
        - Water Pollution
          - 1969 June-1970 (Reel 60, Frame 160)
          - 1967-1969 May (Reel 61, Frame 9)
        - Water Supply (Reel 61, Frame 74)
        - A-Z (Reel 61, Frame 93)
    - General (Reel 61)
      - Governors Conference on Health and Hospital Services (Reel 61, Frame 123)
      - Health Planning Commission (Reel 61, Frame 129)
      - Health Costs (Reel 61, Frame 136)
      - General (Reel 61, Frame 150)
  - Honorary Designation (Reel 61, Reel 62)
    - 1971-1972 (Reel 61, Frame 197)
    - 1967 January-1969 February (Reel 62, Frame 14)
  - Horse Racing (Reel 62)
    - Flat (Reel 62)
      - Aqueduct (Reel 62, Frame 109)
      - State Racing Commission (Reel 62, Frame 115)
      - General (Reel 62, Frame 145)
    - Harness (Reel 62)
      - State Harness Racing Commission (Reel 62, Frame 150)
        - Whipping of Race Horses (Reel 62, Frame 152)
        - General (Reel 62, Frame 155)
      - General (Reel 62, Frame 163)
  - Housing (Reel 62, Reel 63, Reel 64)
    - Division of (Reel 62)
      - Commendation, letters of (Reel 62, Frame 168)
      - General (Reel 62, Frame 169)
    - Urban Renewal (Reel 62, Reel 63)
      - Buffalo-Amherst Corridor & Waterfront (Reel 62, Frame 212)
      - Office of Common Affairs (Reel 62, Frame 229)
      - Office of Urban Innovation (Reel 62, Frame 240)
      - Urban Action Center (Reel 62)
        - 1967 October-1970 (Reel 62, Frame 243)
        - 1967 January-October (Reel 63, Frame 12)
      - Urban Development Corp (Reel 63, Frame 17)
      - General (Reel 63, Frame 82)
    - Construction and Repairs (Reel 63, Reel 64)
      - General (Reel 63, Frame 205)
      - Low & Middle Income (Reel 63, Frame 222)
      - Projects
        - Battery Park City
          - 1969 October-1970 (Reel 63, Frame 255)
          - 1967-1969 September (Reel 64, Frame 12)
        - Co-op City (Reel 64, Frame 21)
        - A-Z (Reel 64, Frame 29)
        - General (Reel 64, Frame 65)
    - Rent Control (Reel 64, Frame 70)
      - Tenant Problems (Reel 64, Frame 83)
      - General (Reel 64, Frame 140)
  - Insurance (Reel 64, Reel 65, Reel 66)
    - Department of (Reel 64)
      - Commendation, Letters of (Reel 64, Frame 180)
      - General (Reel 64, Frame 183)
    - General (Reel 64, Reel 65, Reel 66)
      - Auto (Reel 64)
      - No-Fault (Reel 64, Frame 215)
      - Liability
        - 1969-1970 (Reel 64, Frame 247)
        - 1967-1968 (Reel 65, Frame 12)
      - Fire (Reel 65, Frame 25)
      - Health Aged & Medicaid (Reel 65, Frame 61)
      - Health
        - Universal (Reel 66, Frame 12)
        - General (Reel 66, Frame 77)
    - General (Reel 66, Frame 113)
    - General (Reel 66, Frame 168)
    - State Commission To Investigate (Reel 66, Frame 160)
  - Judiciary (Reel 66, Reel 67)
    - Courts (Reel 66, Reel 67)
      - Court of Appeals (Reel 66, Frame 200)
      - Court of Claims (Reel 66, Frame 207)
      - Family Court (Reel 66, Frame 223)
      - Supreme Court
        - 1969-1970 (Reel 66, Frame 244)
        - 1967-1968 (Reel 67, Frame 12)
      - General (Reel 67, Frame 40)
    - General (Reel 67)
      - Judicial Conference (Reel 67, Frame 47)
      - Jury Duty (Reel 67, Frame 68)
      - Litigation Cases (Reel 67, Frame 72)
      - General (Reel 67, Frame 116)
  - Labor (Reel 67, Reel 68, Reel 69, Reel 70, Reel 71)
    - Department of (Reel 67, Reel 68)
      - Commendation Letters (Reel 67, Frame 206)
      - Labor Relations Act (Reel 67, Frame 218)
      - Labor Relations Board (Reel 67, Frame 219)
      - Manpower
        - 1969 May-1970 (Reel 67, Frame 222)
        - 1967-1969 April (Reel 68, Frame 12)
      - Migratory Labor (Reel 68, Frame 56)
      - General (Reel 68, Frame 92)
    - Benefits (Reel 68, Reel 69)
      - Unemployment Insurance
        - 1968-1970 (Reel 68, Frame 134)
        - 1967 (Reel 69, Frame 13)
      - Workman's Compensation (Reel 69, Frame 61)
    - Mediation & Arbitration (Reel 69, Frame 96)
    - Minimum Wage (Reel 69, Frame 103)
    - Social Security (Reel 69, Frame 109)
    - Strikes (Reel 69, Reel 70)
      - Fireman (Reel 69, Frame 136)
      - Fuel Oil Drivers, New York City (Reel 69, Frame 172)
      - General Electric (Reel 69, Frame 175)
      - Gravediggers (Reel 69, Frame 181)
      - Longshoreman (Reel 69, Frame 193)
      - Mental Hygiene Institute (Reel 69, Frame 212)
      - Postal (Reel 69, Frame 245)
      - Railroads (Reel 69, Frame 248)
      - Sanitation (Reel 70, Frame 13)
      - Teachers (Reel 70, Frame 50)
      - General (Reel 70, Frame 90)
    - Unemployment (Reel 70)
      - Division of (Reel 70)
        - Council, Employment & Unemployment (Reel 70, Frame 115)
        - Youth Employment & Services (Reel 70, Frame 132)
        - Employment Services (Reel 70, Frame 147)
        - Unemployment Insurance (Reel 70, Frame 153)
        - General (Reel 70, Frame 172)
      - General (Reel 70, Frame 183)
      - Workmen's Compensation (Reel 70, Frame 202)
    - General (Reel 70)
      - Governor's Workshop on Job Opportunity (Reel 70, Frame 212)
      - Industrial Code 4-1967 (Reel 70, Frame 233)
      - Labor Management Agreement, Buffalo (Reel 70, Frame 243)
    - General (Reel 71, Frame 13)
  - Law (Reel 71, Reel 72, Reel 73)
    - Department of (Reel 71)
      - Commendation, letters of (Reel 71, Frame 77)
    - General (Reel 71, Reel 72, Reel 73)
      - General (Reel 71, Frame 87)
      - Abortion Law (Reel 71, Frame 98)
      - Alcoholic Beverage Control (Reel 71, Frame 129)
      - American Flag (Desecration of) (Reel 71, Frame 134)
      - Constitutional Convention (Reel 71, Frame 155)
      - Daylight Saving Time (Reel 72, Frame 12)
      - Domestic Relations (Reel 72, Frame 13)
      - Election (Reel 72)
        - 18 year old voters (Reel 72, Frame 47)
        - Election General (Reel 72, Frame 107)
      - Holidays (Reel 72, Frame 163)
      - Obscene Literature (Reel 72, Frame 189)
      - Revised Penal Law
        - 1967 October-1970 (Reel 72, Frame 235)
        - 1967 January-September (Reel 73, Frame 12)
      - Sabbath Law (Reel 73, Frame 20)
      - General (Reel 73, Frame 28)
  - Legislature (Reel 73)
    - Federal (Reel 73)
      - Congress (Reel 73, Frame 63)
      - U.S. Senate (Reel 73, Frame 76)
      - General (Reel 73, Frame 80)
    - State (Reel 73)
      - Committee A-L-L (Reel 73, Frame 84)
      - Annual Message (Reel 73, Frame 110)
      - Special Message (Reel 73, Frame 133)
      - Special Session (Reel 73, Frame 149)
      - General (Reel 73, Frame 173)
  - Licensing (Reel 73, Reel 74)
    - Auto Mechanics (Reel 73, Frame 192)
    - Firearms (Reel 73, Frame 194)
    - Liquor (Reel 73, Frame 199)
    - Medicine (Reel 73, Frame 238)
    - Nurses (Reel 73, Frame 240)
    - Real Estate (Reel 73, Frame 246)
    - General (Reel 74)
      - A-Z (Reel 74, Frame 17)
      - 1967-1970 (Reel 74, Frame 27)
  - Mental Hygiene (Reel 74, Reel 75, Reel 76, Reel 77, Reel 78)
    - Department of (Reel 74)
      - Commendation, letters of (Reel 74, Frame 28)
    - National Treatment Centers Bedford Hills & Saw Mill Rehabilitation Centers (Reel 74, Frame 35)
      - Brooklyn (Reel 74, Frame 48)
      - Freeport (Reel 74, Frame 62)
      - Howard Beach (Reel 74, Frame 78)
      - Staten Island (Reel 74, Frame 130)
      - Van Dam Street, Long Island City (Reel 74, Frame 137)
      - Yonkers (Reel 74, Frame 158)
      - General (Reel 74, Frame 166)
    - Narcotics (Reel 74, Reel 75, Reel 76)
      - Addiction Control Commission (Reel 74, Reel 75)
        - 1969-1970 (Reel 74, Frame 213)
        - 1968-1970 (Reel 75, Frame 12)
      - General (Reel 75, Reel 76)
        - 1970 August-December (Reel 75, Frame 61)
        - 1967-1970 July (Reel 76, Frame 11)
    - Department of (Reel 76, Reel 77)
      - Reports (Reel 76, Frame 203)
      - General (Reel 76, Reel 77)
        - 1970 (Reel 76, Frame 238)
        - 1967-1969 (Reel 77, Frame 13)
    - Institutions (Reel 77)
      - Binghamton (Reel 77, Frame 29)
      - Bronx (Reel 77, Frame 30)
      - Brooklyn (Reel 77, Frame 46)
      - Buffalo (Reel 77, Frame 47)
      - Central Islip (Reel 77, Frame 48)
      - Creedmor (Reel 77, Frame 51)
      - Gowanda (Reel 77, Frame 65)
      - Harlem (Reel 77, Frame 66)
      - Hudson River (Reel 77, Frame 69)
      - Kings (Reel 77, Frame 74)
      - Maimonides (Reel 77, Frame 77)
      - Manhattan (Reel 77, Frame 79)
      - Marcy (Reel 77, Frame 82)
      - Middletown (Reel 77, Frame 85)
      - Onondoga (Reel 77, Frame 88)
      - Pilgrim (Reel 77, Frame 93)
      - Rochester (Reel 77, Frame 97)
      - Rockland (Reel 77, Frame 106)
      - St. Lawrence (Reel 77, Frame 109)
      - Suffolk (Reel 77, Frame 114)
      - Westchester (Reel 77, Frame 117)
      - Willowbrook (Reel 77, Frame 126)
      - A-Z (Reel 77, Frame 155)
      - General (Reel 77, Frame 189)
    - General (Reel 77, Reel 78)
      - Mental Retardation (Reel 77, Frame 197)
      - General
        - 1969-1970 (Reel 77, Frame 229)
        - 1967-1968 (Reel 78, Frame 15)
  - Military and Naval (Reel 78, Reel 79)
    - Armories (Reel 78)
      - Sumner Avenue Armory (Reel 78, Frame 24)
    - Air National Guard (Reel 78, Frame 48)
    - General (Reel 78, Frame 51)
    - Division of (Reel 78)
      - New York Naval Militia (Reel 78, Frame 96)
      - Affairs (Reel 78, Frame 97)
    - Installations (Reel 78)
      - Brooklyn Navy Yard (Reel 78, Frame 113)
      - Floyd Bennet Field (Reel 78, Frame 115)
      - Griffiss Air Force Base (Reel 78, Frame 127)
      - Stewart Air Force Base (Reel 78, Frame 145)
      - Fort Totten (Reel 78, Frame 170)
      - A-Z (Reel 78, Frame 196)
      - General (Reel 78, Frame 215)
    - Federal (Reel 78, Reel 79)
      - ABM Issue (Reel 78, Frame 232)
      - U.S. Air Force (Reel 78, Frame 243)
      - U.S. Army
        - 1970 (Reel 78, Frame 246)
        - 1967-1969 (Reel 79, Frame 12)
      - Space Flights (Reel 79, Frame 98)
      - U.S. Navy Naval Applies Science Lab (Reel 79, Frame 116)
      - U.S. Navy (Reel 79, Frame 128)
  - Motor Vehicles (Reel 79)
    - Department of (Reel 79)
      - Commendation, letters of (Reel 79, Frame 140)
      - Departmental Activities Reports (Reel 79, Frame 144)
      - Operator's License (Reel 79, Frame 164)
      - Reports of Fatal Accidents (Reel 79, Frame 187)
      - General (Reel 79, Frame 195)
  - Organizations
    Arrangement
    Alphabetical by title.
    - Adirondack Park Association - American Publishers Association (Reel 80)
    - American Rehabilitation Foundation - Brooklyn Bar Association (Reel 81)
    - Brooklyn Association for Mental Health - Citizens Union of the City of New York (Reel 82)
    - Civil Services Employees Association - Dal (Reel 83)
    - Dan - Governor's Conference Gifts (Reel 84)
    - Governor's Conference (1967-1970) - Gre (Reel 85)
    - Gri - Je (Reel 86)
    - Jo - Muscular Dystrophy Association (Reel 87)
    - Mus - National J (Reel 88)
    - National K - New York City Council of Churches (Reel 89)
    - New York Council of Retail Merchants - Police Organizations (Reel 90)
    - Po - Ro (Reel 91)
    - Roc - Tr (Reel 92)
    - Tu - Young Republicans Club of New York (Reel 93)
    - Young Republican Club of Armstrong County (Reel 94, Frame 12)
    - Zonta International Club of Buffalo (Reel 94, Frame 52)
  - Parks & Recreational Facilities (Reel 94)
    - Parks (Reel 94)
      - Adirondack Mountains National Park (Reel 94, Frame 52)
      - Erie Canal (Reel 94, Frame 86)
      - Gateway National Park (Reel 94, Frame 91)
      - Hamlin Beach (Reel 94, Frame 92)
      - Hudson Highland (Reel 94, Frame 101)
      - Keuka Lake (Reel 94, Frame 102)
      - Minnewaska (Reel 94, Frame 105)
      - Nickelson (Reel 94, Frame 109)
      - Saratoga (Reel 94, Frame 123)
      - A-Z (Reel 94, Frame 126)
    - General (Reel 94, Frame 155)
      - Winter Sports (Reel 94, Frame 166)
      - Valcour Island (Reel 94, Frame 182)
      - General (Reel 94, Frame 198)
  - Personal Administration (Reel 94, Reel 95, Reel 96, Reel 97)
    - Civil Service Department (Reel 94, Reel 95)
      - Class and Comp.
      - Reallocation
        - 1968-1970 (Reel 94, Frame 234)
        - 1967 (Reel 95, Frame 11)
      - General (Reel 95, Frame 21)
      - Civil Service (Reel 95)
        - Commission (Reel 95, Frame 25)
        - Examinatons (Reel 95)
          - Disqualification (Reel 95, Frame 52)
          - General (Reel 95, Frame 59)
      - Personal Services (Reel 95)
        - Merit Awards (Reel 95, Frame 83)
        - Training (Reel 95, Frame 112)
        - General (Reel 95, Frame 128)
      - Public Employees Relations Board (Reel 95, Frame 131)
      - Resolutions (Reel 95)
      - Alfred E. Smith Fellows (Reel 95, Frame 187)
    - State Employees (Reel 95, Reel 96)
      - Attendance Rules
        - 1969-1970 (Reel 95, Frame 234)
        - 1967-1968 (Reel 96, Frame 13)
      - Blood Donor Program (Reel 96, Frame 28)
      - Grievance (Reel 96)
        - Appointments (Reel 96, Frame 30)
        - Reinstatements (Reel 96, Frame 41)
        - Termination (Reel 96, Frame 57)
        - Others (Reel 96, Frame 71)
      - Retirement (Reel 96, Frame 92)
      - Salaries (Reel 96, Frame 131)
      - Savings Bond Corp (Reel 96, Frame 169)
      - General (Reel 96, Frame 172)
    - Teachers (Reel 96)
      - Retirement (Reel 96, Frame 217)
      - General (Reel 96, Frame 234)
    - Local Government (Reel 96)
      - City (Reel 96, Frame 241)
      - General (Reel 96, Frame 251)
    - General (Reel 97)
      - Governor's Conference on Public Employees Relations (Reel 97, Frame 12)
      - Taylor Law (Reel 97, Frame 18)
      - General (Reel 97, Frame 121)
  - Politics (Reel 97, Reel 98)
    - 1970 Gubernatorial (Reel 97, Frame 145)
    - Senator Goodell (Reel 98, Frame 13)
    - 1968 Presidency (Reel 98, Frame 115)
    - Mayoralty Election in New York City (Reel 98, Frame 159)
    - General (Reel 98, Frame 179)
  - Property (Reel 98, Reel 99)
    - Federal (Reel 98, Reel 99)
      - Surplus Property
        - 1969-1970 (Reel 98, Frame 239)
        - 1967-1968 (Reel 99, Frame 13)
      - General (Reel 99, Frame 39)
    - State (Reel 99)
      - Acquisition & Purchase (Reel 99)
        - Highways (Reel 99, Frame 51)
        - Parks (Reel 99, Frame 69)
        - Lake Minnewoska (Reel 99, Frame 80)
        - General (Reel 99, Frame 107)
      - General (Reel 99, Frame 114)
  - Public Safety (Reel 99, Reel 100, Reel 101, Reel 102)
    - Federal (Reel 99, Frame 136)
    - State Police (Reel 99, Reel 100)
      - Division of Troopers (Reel 99)
        - Letters of Commendation (Reel 99, Frame 140)
        - Complaints (Reel 99, Frame 155)
        - Graduation (Reel 99, Frame 168)
        - General (Reel 99, Frame 169)
      - General (Reel 99, Reel 100)
        - 1969-1970 (Reel 99, Frame 203)
        - 1967-1968 (Reel 100, Frame 12)
    - Highway Safety (Reel 100, Reel 101)
      - Drinking Drivers (Reel 100, Frame 34)
      - Interdepartmental Traffic Safety Commission (Reel 100, Frame 44)
      - Safety Car (Reel 100, Frame 106)
      - Traffic Safety Council (Reel 100, Frame 128)
      - Traffic Signals
        - 1969-1970 (Reel 100, Frame 244)
        - 1967-1968 (Reel 101, Frame 12)
      - General (Reel 101, Frame 19)
    - State (Reel 101, Reel 102)
      - Crime (Reel 101, Reel 102)
        - 1969-1970 (Reel 101, Frame 103)
        - 1967-1968 (Reel 102, Frame 13)
    - General (Reel 102)
      - Fire (Reel 102, Frame 114)
      - Local Police Reports (Reel 102, Frame 154)
      - General (Reel 102, Frame 163)
  - Public Utilities (Reel 102, Reel 103, Reel 104, Reel 105)
    - Communications (Reel 102, Reel 103)
      - Cable Television Report (Reel 102, Frame 204)
      - Telephone (Reel 102, Frame 234)
      - General (Reel 103, Frame 18)
    - Fuel (Reel 103)
      - Gas (Reel 103, Frame 45)
      - Fuel Oil (Reel 103, Frame 84)
      - General (Reel 103, Frame 85)
    - Power (Reel 103, Reel 104)
      - Atomic Blemheim-Gilboa (Reel 103, Frame 90)
      - Cayuga Lake (Reel 103, Frame 95)
      - Con Ed Cornwall Palisades-Storm King (Reel 103, Frame 100)
      - General (Reel 103, Frame 115)
      - Blackout (Reel 103, Frame 149)
      - Electric
        - 1969-1970 (Reel 103, Frame 164)
        - 1967-1968 (Reel 104, Frame 16)
      - General (Reel 104, Frame 48)
    - Transportation (Reel 104)
      - Bond Issue (Reel 104, Frame 70)
      - Railroads (Reel 104)
        - Full Crew Laws (Reel 104, Frame 125)
        - Long Island (Reel 104, Frame 126)
        - New Haven (Reel 104, Frame 130)
        - General (Reel 104, Frame 141)
      - General (Reel 104, Frame 149)
    - General (Reel 104, Reel 105)
      - Interstate Commerce Commission (Reel 104, Frame 168)
      - Public Service Commission
        - 1968-1970 (Reel 104, Frame 175)
        - 1967 (Reel 105, Frame 9)
      - General (Reel 105, Frame 55)
  - Public Works (Reel 105, Reel 106)
    - Department of (Reel 105)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 105, Frame 60)
    - Buildings (Reel 105)
      - Harlem (Reel 105, Frame 62)
      - General (Reel 105, Frame 76)
    - Canals & Waterways (Reel 105)
      - Fire Island (Reel 105, Frame 85)
      - General (Reel 105, Frame 94)
    - Highways (Reel 105, Reel 106)
      - Route 87 (Reel 105, Frame 117)
      - Local Roads (Reel 105, Frame 120)
      - Long Island Sound Bridge (Reel 105, Frame 128)
      - La Salle Express Way (Reel 105, Frame 160)
      - Lower Hudson Valley Expressway (Reel 106, Frame 14)
      - NU Way (Reel 106, Frame 18)
      - Route 117 (Reel 106, Frame 22)